嗨  本
Hi, Ben.
这孩子急着嘘嘘
We have a bathroom emergency.
去吧
Go ahead.
去之前问一句
Before we do,
里面没有乔伊的"浪漫"杂志吧
are any of Joey's special "romance" magazines in there?
-没有  -可以去了
- No. - Okay, all clear.
谢谢  菲比
Thanks, Phoebe.
我是瑞秋
That's Rachel.
不过随便啦
But whatever.
可以帮我个大忙吗
Could you do me a big favor?
院长办公室召开紧急会议
The dean's office just called and said there was an urgent meeting.
你能帮我照看本一小时吗
Can you watch Ben for an hour?
-莫妮卡呢  -她不在家
- What about Monica? - She isn't home.
就我一个人吗
So it would just be me alone?
还有本
Ben would be there.
怎么了
What's the matter?
只是...
Well that... you know it's just uh,
我以前从来没跟他单独待过
I've never done that before. Me and him, alone.
他又不是前科犯
Rach, he's not an ex-con.
好  好...
Okay, okay...
-我要陪他做什么  -聊聊天
- What do I do with him? - I don't know, talk to him.
陪他玩  保他不死就行
Entertain him. Keep him alive.
-好  -本  来
- Okay. - Ben, come here.
我要把你留在这儿
I'm gonna leave you here
和瑞秋阿姨一起待一小时  好吗
with Aunt Rachel for about an hour, okay?
可以吗
Gonna be okay?
-可以  -我没跟你说话
- I think so. - I wasn't talking to you.
我们见的第二位牧师如何  我还蛮喜欢他的
What about the second minister we meet with? I kind of liked him.
你是指口沫横飞那位
You mean the spitter?
别这样  他喷得也没那么厉害
Come on. He wasn't that bad.
你说起来容易  你到时候有面纱遮脸
Easy for you to say, you'd be wearing a veil.
-那第三位呢  -他一直瞪着你的胸部看
- What about the third guy? - He kept staring at your chest.
这你能怪他吗
Can you blame him?
我不希望我说"我愿意"时...
I don't like the idea of me saying, "I do"...
他心里想着"我也愿意"
...while he's thinking, "I'd do it too."
-这个问题还是有待解决  -什么问题
- Well, then we still have a problem. - With what?
我们需要找人帮我们主持婚礼
We're trying to find someone to perform our wedding
但他们要么无趣  要么烦人
and they're all either boring or annoying
要么一直盯着我的咪咪看
or can't stop staring at the ladies.
应该找我们其中一人来主婚
You should have one of us do it.
我们是要正经八百地结婚
Phoebe, we're getting "married" married,
不是小孩过家家
not "6th-grade" married.
我是说正经的
No, it's a real thing.
任何人都能在网络上被任命为牧师
Anyone can be ordained on the Internet
然后主持婚礼
and perform weddings and stuff.
我要
I call it!
干嘛  这可是我的主意
What? It was my idea!
真心谢谢你们  但你们谁也不能替我们主婚
Guys, thank you very much, but neither of you is marrying us.
现在喊"我要"都不管用了吗
Does calling it not mean anything anymore?
我们要找一位正规的牧师
We're having a legitimate clergy member.
我说的正规是指  他得是同性恋...
And when I say legitimate, I mean gay...
而且能控制住不喷口水
...and in control of his saliva.
本  你还是个小婴儿的时候
Ben, you know, when you were a baby...
我们经常待在一起
...you and I used to hang out all the time.
那时我是你爸的女朋友
I was your daddy's girlfriend.
可你现在不是了
But you're not anymore.
-对  我不是了  -因为你们当时分开了
- No, I'm not. - Because you guys were on a break...
喂  我们没...
Hey, we were not on a...
-我爸什么时候会回来  -再过52分钟
- When's my daddy coming back? - 52 minutes.
你没有兄弟姐妹是吧
So no brothers or sisters, huh?
我有两个姐妹  我们会互相折磨
You know what, I had two sisters and we just tortured each other.
-真的吗  说说看  -我们会...
- Really? Like how? - Well, you know, we would...
重复另一个人说的每一句话
...we'd repeat everything the other said...
或是从衣柜跳出去吓人
...or we'd jump out of closets to scare each other...
或是把糖换成盐
...or switch the sugar with salt
让别人把盐洒到麦片里
so they put salt on their cereal.
这个好玩
That's a good one.
-你喜欢吗  -是  你很有意思
- Yeah, you like that one? - Yeah, you're funny.
我很有意思
I'm funny?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我有一大堆这种故事
Well, hey, I got a ton of these.
拿一枚25分硬币
You take a quarter...
把边缘涂黑
...and you blacken the edge, right?
然后说  我打赌  你拿这枚硬币从额头
And then you say to a person, "I bet you can't roll this quarter
滚到下巴  一定会离开你的脸
from your forehead to your chin without it leaving your face."
等他们真的滚了
And when they do it,
就会在脸正中央留下一条黑线
they're left with a line down the center of their face.
我可以对你这样吗
Can I do it to you?
本  我是幽默  但我不笨
I'm funny, Ben, but I'm not stupid.
你们找到婚礼主持了吗
So did you find anyone to marry you yet?
没有  但"痴想莫妮卡"牧师打电话来了
No, but "Horny for Monica" minister called...
想知道我们是否还在一起
...wondering if we're still together.
-我们找不到合适的人选了  -那就让我来
- We'll never find anybody. - Then let me do it.
-乔伊  -我考虑过了
- Joey... - I've been thinking about it.
我是个演员  所以在人前发言不会紧张
I'm an actor, so I won't get nervous talking in front of people.
我不会喷口水  也不会瞪着莫妮卡的胸部看
I won't spit and I won't stare at Monica's breasts.
大家都知道我对臀部情有独钟
Everyone knows I'm an ass man.
-那倒是真的  -最重要的是
- That's true. - The most important thing...
你们不必找个几乎不了解你们的陌生人
...is, it won't be some stranger who barely knows you.
而是我这个朋友  我保证会出色完成任务
It'll be me. And I swear, I'll do a really good job.
还有  我爱你们  这件事对我意义重大
Plus, I love you guys and it would really mean a lot to me.
还挺带劲的
Might be kind of cool.
-我可以主婚吗  -好吧  可以
- So I can do it? - Yeah, you can do it.
太棒了
All right! Okay!
好  我要开始准备演说了
Okay, I gotta get started on my speech.
等一下
Wait a minute.
-网络上任命的牧师可以做爱吧  -对
- Internet ministers can have sex, right? - Yeah.
我要找你算账
I have a bone to pick with you.
-惨了  -没错
- Uh-oh. - Yes.
本学会了一个恶作剧
Ben learned a little trick.
-他是不是...  -对  是的
- Oh, did he pull the old...? - That's right. That's right.
在马桶座上包上保鲜膜
Saran wrap on the toilet seat...
这样尿尿就会喷得到处都是
...so the pee goes everywhere.
-那招啊  -对  就是那招
- Oh, that. - Yeah, that.
你知道我最恨恶作剧了
You know I hate practical jokes.
恶作剧又毒又蠢
They're mean, they're stupid
我不想让我儿子学这种东西
and I don't want my son learning them.
别这样
Come on.
马桶包保鲜膜  你没觉得有一点点好笑吗
Saran wrap on the toilet seat? Isn't that just a little funny?
我当时赤着脚
I was barefoot.
你只有教他马桶这一招  对吧
Tell me, the toilet thing is the only thing you taught him, right?
对
Yes.
向乔伊·崔比安尼牧师问好吧
Say hello to Reverend Joey Tribbiani.
-你被任命了  -对
- You got ordained? - Yeah.
我刚刚下网  网上有好多色情片
Just got off the Internet. Man, there's a lot of porn out there.
这就是我们的牧师
Our minister.
我已经写好了主婚词  要听吗
I started on what I'm gonna say for the ceremony. Want to hear it?
注意  这只是第一稿  所以...
Listen, this is just the first draft, so...
今天我们齐聚一堂  在这个喜悦的场合
"We are gathered here today on this joyous occasion...
庆祝莫妮卡和钱德勒之间独一无二的爱情
...to celebrate the special love that Monica and Chandler share.
这份爱基于付出与接受
It is a love based on giving and receiving...
拥有与分享
...as well as having and sharing.
他们付出并拥有的爱被分享并接受了
And the love that they give and have is shared and received.
借着这样的拥有与付出...
And through this having and giving...
分享与接受...
...and sharing and receiving...
我们同样分享  付出
...we too can share and love
拥有...
and have...
还有接受
...and receive."
要不要打电话给喷口水的那位
Should we call the spitter?
瑞秋
Hey, Rachel.
真没想到  你怎么来了
What a nice surprise. What are you doing here?
我正好走到附近  经过你家
I was just in the neighborhood and I passed by your building
我就想  卡罗尔和可爱的小本
and I thought to myself, "What's up with Carol...
不知道怎么样
...and sweet little Ben?"
-真好  请进  -好
- That's nice. Well, come on in. - Okay.
我来煮咖啡  我们可以聊聊天
I'll make some coffee and we can chat.
好啊  很好
I'd love that. I would love that.
可爱的小本呢
So where is sweet little Ben?
我想和小...
I would love to have a little...
找到他了
I found him!
好好笑  过来
Very funny. Come here.
我过来就是想找你谈这件事
That is exactly why I've come here to talk to you, okay?
-瑞秋  要加糖吗  -好  不要...
- Rachel, you want sugar? - Yes, but...
我的咖啡要不要加糖
Do I want sugar in my coffee?
不要  只加牛奶就好  谢谢
No, just some milk would be good, Carol. Thanks.
记得我昨天教你的那些东西吗
Remember all that stuff I taught you yesterday?
"记得我昨天教你的那些东西吗"
"Remember all that stuff I taught you yesterday?"
-别学我  -"别学我"
- Don't do that. - "Don't do that."
你爸爸不喜欢恶作剧
Seriously, your dad doesn't like pranks.
"你爸爸不喜欢恶作剧"
"Seriously, your dad doesn't like pranks."
-该死  -"该死"
- Oh, damn it! - "Oh, damn it!"
别学这句
No! Don't say that.
-该死  -你还是接着重复我的话吧
- Damn it! - Go back to repeating.
-该死  -可恶
- Damn it! - Oh, crap!
"可恶"
"Oh, crap!"
好  我又写了几句词  要听吗
Okay, I got some more written, ready?
好啊
Yeah, okay.
当我想起这两位付出者
"When I think of the love that these two givers
和接受者所分享的爱...
and receivers share...
我禁不住嫉妒他们将来一生的拥有  相爱
...I can't help but envy the lifetime ahead of having and loving...
与付出  我想不出这儿要用什么词
...and giving..." And then I can't think of a good word for right here.
-用"接受"如何  -对
- How about "receiving"? - Yes!
乔伊  不是说你写的词不好
See, Joe, not that that's not great...
但朋友主婚的好处就在于
...but one cool thing about having a friend perform the ceremony...
婚礼可以围绕我们展开
...is that it can be about us.
更具个人特色  你可以讲讲我们的小故事
It can be more personal. You can tell stories about us.
好  我可以讲你们当年在伦敦勾搭上了
Okay! Maybe I'll talk about London, when you hooked up.
当然我不会说"勾搭上了"
Only I won't say "hooked up"...
我会说  他们美丽的旅程...
...l'll say, "began their beautiful journey...
-这就对了  -一"炮"打响
- There you go. ...by doing it."
-乔伊  -好吧
- Joe. - Okay, all right.
你们是怎么开始的
So how did it happen?
你们穿越人群  四目相对
Did your eyes meet across the room...
然后你们泡在浴缸里  她喂你吃草莓
...then you're in the bathtub and she's feeding you strawberries?
-那不是你和伴娘的风流往事吗  -对
- Isn't that what happened to you? - Yeah!
我称其为"伦敦派"
I call that "London style."
我们不是这么开始的
That didn't happen with us.
你应该顺口承认下来
Maybe you should say it is,
因为"伦敦派"听着很带劲
because "London style" sounds nice.
好吧
Okay, uh...
那天晚上我很郁闷
I was really sad that night
因为有个家伙以为我是罗斯他妈
because this guy thought I was Ross' mom.
钱德勒对我很体贴  一直安慰我...
And Chandler was really sweet and he consoled me and...
-我们喝得烂醉  -这就对了  宝贝
...we drank too much. - Yeah, baby.
我很绅士地
I was a perfect gentleman
陪她走回酒店房间  道了晚安
and I walked her to her hotel room and said good night.
-但后来...  -这就对了  宝贝
- But then, later that night... - Yeah, baby.
可爱的睡衣  真想在伦敦过得多采多姿是吧
Cute P.J.s. Really living it up here in London, huh?
我还以为不会有人来了  毕竟现在都...
Well, I wasn't exactly expecting company after...
9点15分了
...9:15.
乔伊在吗
Is Joey here?
我之前见他搂着伴娘  抱着一桶草莓
Last I saw he was with a bridesmaid and a bucket of strawberries.
那个
So...
你不会还在为那家伙的话生气吧
You're not still upset about what that guy told you, are you?
换你不生气吗
Wouldn't you be?
你这段时间情绪很不稳定
It's been a really emotional time
又喝了不少
and you've had a lot to drink...
你就别再纠结了  好吗
You have to let that go, okay?
你是今晚宴会上最美的女人
You were the most beautiful woman in the room tonight.
真的吗
Really?
开玩笑  你是全世界最美的女人
You kidding? You're the most beautiful woman in most rooms...
怎么回事
Whoa, what's going on?
我们亲嘴了
You and I just made out!
-我们亲嘴了  -现在没有啊
- You and I are making out? - Not anymore.
可我们之前没亲过
But we don't do that.
我知道  我觉得亲一亲会很好玩
I know, I thought it would be fun.
你醉到什么程度
How drunk are you?
醉到知道自己想亲你
Enough to know I want to do this.
但头脑还够清醒  你不必感觉占了我的便宜
Not so drunk that you should feel guilty about taking advantage.
醉得刚刚好
That's the perfect amount.
-你知道奇怪在哪儿吗  -哪儿
- You know what's weird? - What?
-感觉一点都不奇怪  -对啊
- This doesn't feel weird. - I know.
你的吻功很棒
You're a really good kisser.
我吻过不止四个女人
Well, I have kissed over four women.
-想钻到被窝里吗  -好啊
- Want to get under the covers? - Okay.
你动作太快了吧
Wow, you are really fast!
你觉得我速度快  这对我来说是好兆头
It bodes well for me that speed impresses you.
-我们要裸程相见了  -对
- We're gonna see each other naked. - Yep.
-同时看吧  -数到三
- You want to do it at the same time? - Count of three?
一  二  三
One, two, three.
看来我们的友谊算是彻底毁了
Well, I think it's safe to say our friendship is effectively ruined.
反正我们本来也没那么要好
Eh, we weren't that close anyway.
乔伊  乔伊  乔伊...
Joey, Joey, Joey...!
乔伊  我在看电影...
Hey, Joe. I was just watching a movie...
老兄  对不起
Oh, dude, I'm so sorry.
不是你想的那样
No! No! No!
没事  我还跟伴娘在一起
No, no, no! It's cool, I'm still with my bridesmaid.
安全套在哪儿
Where are the condoms you brought?
在那边  我的包里
In my bag over there.
可以留一个给我吗
Could you leave me one?
就你自己用吗
For just you?
对
Yeah.
好吧  给你  老兄
All right. There you go, buddy.
好好快活吧
Go nuts.
原来是怎么回事啊
That's what that was?
如果我当时没给你留套会怎样
Can you imagine if I hadn't left you that last one?
你们俩可能就没机会在一起了
You two might've never gotten together.
如果我照原来计划招了妓女上去会怎样
Can you imagine if I had sent that hooker like I was gonna?
这就是命运的安排
It's like it was in the stars.
是啊  你们注定要在一起
Yeah, totally meant to be.
告诉他你那晚原先是要去找谁
Tell him who you originally wanted to hook up with that night.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
什么
What?
你原先是要去找谁
Who did you originally want to hook up with?
好吧  不要生气
Okay, fine, but please don't be upset.
我当时真的很郁闷  而且烂醉如泥
I was really depressed, okay? And really drunk.
我想做点毫无意义的蠢事  只想找个炮友
I wanted something stupid and meaningless. I just wanted sex.
所以那晚我到你们房间...
So, when I went to your room that night...
其实是想找乔伊
...I was actually looking for Joey.
这就对了  宝贝
Yeah, baby.
不  宝贝
No, baby.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你是去找乔伊的
So you came to the room looking for Joey?
你有打算告诉我吗
Were you planning on telling me this?
没有  我觉得这不重要
No, I didn't think it was important.
这不重要  这不重要
It's not important? It's not important?
如果没那个伴娘  你嫁的会是他而不是我
If it wasn't for a bridesmaid, you'd be marrying him not me.
你知道我有多高兴
Do you know how unbelievably glad I am
乔伊当时不在吗
that Joey was not there that night?
虽然我是神职人员  可是我还是有感觉的
I'm a man of the cloth, but I still have feelings.
现在你不可能替我们主婚了
There's no way you're doing this wedding now, okay?
什么  这不公平  又不是我的错
What? That's not fair. It's not my fault.
我当时和伴娘在一起
I was off with my bridesmaid.
而且你怎么知道我会答应她
And who's to say I would've said yes?
我肯定会答应的
I mean, I would've said yes.
你把这件事看得太严重了
Chandler, you are making way too big a deal out of this.
最后的结局很好啊
Everything worked out okay.
就是觉得别扭
It's just weird, okay?
我可不想在立下婚誓的时候
I don't want to be saying my vows
脑海里浮现你和莫妮卡的在一起的样子
and then having the mental image of you and Monica.
我需要...
I need...
我也不知道我要什么  我出去透透气
I don't know what I need. I need a walk.
等一下  钱德勒  这没什么大不了
Wait, Chandler, come on, it's not a big deal.
对我很重要  你本想和蝙蝠侠上床
It is to me. You wanted to sleep with Batman,
结果用罗宾打发了
and instead you had to settle for Robin.
-这太扯了  -不  罗宾绝对是同性恋
- This is crazy. - No, Robin is so gay.
-我们都说好了  -不再搞恶作剧了
- So now what have we agreed? - No more pranks.
-还有呢  -你和爸爸当时没分开
- What else? - You and Daddy were not on a break.
很好
Very good.
瑞秋  你怎么来了
Rachel, what are you doing here?
来看我好朋友卡罗尔
I'm just visiting my good friend Carol.
-你的好朋友  -对
- Your good friend? - Yeah.
她姓什么
What's her last name?
卡罗尔...
Carol...
-同性恋  -很好
- Lesbian. - Nice.
还有  我脸上那条线
By the way, that line down my face...
今天最后一堂课...
The line that prompted a student...
一个学生对我说
...in my last class of the day to say:
"老兄  你从来不洗脸吗"
"Dude, don't you ever wash your face?"
好吧  我很抱歉没有告诉你
All right I'm sorry. I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
我不准你再教我儿子那些东西了
Listen, I don't want you teaching my son that stuff anymore.
-好吗  -好  好
- Okay? - Fine. Fine.
我一教他那些恶作剧
But I'll have you know that once I taught him that stuff,
他叫我"搞笑的瑞秋阿姨"
he called me "fun Aunt Rachel."
我喜欢做搞笑的瑞秋阿姨
And I loved being fun Aunt Rachel.
我很高兴你们能玩得来  但...
I'm glad you guys were bonding but...
他没有任何兄弟姐妹
Look, he doesn't have any brothers or sisters.
得有人教他这些东西
Somebody has to teach him this stuff.
我没有教他任何正常六岁小孩不该知道的事
I haven't taught him anything a normal 6-year-old doesn't know anyway.
-可恶  -我要走了
- Crap! - I gotta go.
你想要这个酥饼吗
You want this scone?
这是给我的  但它更想和你睡
It came for me but it would rather sleep with you.
别这样  明明什么都没发生
Come on. Nothing even happened.
我只是不想惹你生气
I just don't want you to be upset.
我怎么能不生气
How can I not be upset?
我终于和一位如此难得的女人坠入爱河...
I finally fall in love with this fantastic woman...
可她最初想要的却是你
...and it turns out she wanted you first.
只是某晚的那半小时而已
Yeah, for like a half an hour one night.
钱德勒  她想和你共度一生
Chandler, she wants you for the rest of her life.
我们看着你们  相知相爱在一起
We look at you and we see you together,
就是...
and it just...
很般配  你知道吗
...it fits, you know?
我们知道你们一定会相伴到老
And you just know it's gonna last forever.
你就该说这些话才对
That's what you should say.
什么
What?
你给我们主婚的时候  就该说这段话
When you're marrying us, that's what you should say.
真的  我可以替你们主婚吗
Really? I could do it?
我很希望你替我们主婚
I'd love you to do it.
不过你到时就要说那段话  一字不差
But those are the words. Those exact words.
我记不太清了  不过...
Well, I don't remember exactly but...
基本上是关于拥有与付出
...it's pretty much about having and giving
分享与接受
and sharing and receiving.
-你们两个没事了  -是啊
- So you guys doing okay? - Yeah.
我们谈过了  我知道自己反应过度了
We talked and Monica made me see that I overreacted a little bit.
生命中有些事情更加重要
Some things in life are more important.
这就对了  宝贝
Yeah, baby.
很高兴你们没事了  但我一直在想...
I'm really glad you guys are okay, but I just keep thinking...
如果你们两个在一起会是什么样子
...what would've happened if you two had hooked up.
亲爱的  晚饭好了
Honey, dinner's ready!
我的小厨师今晚给我做了什么
What's my little chef got for me tonight?
你最喜欢的
Your favorite.
奶酪油炸食品
Fried stuff with cheese.
做了许多许多
And lots of it!
谢谢  亲爱的
Thanks, sweetheart.
来亲一个
Give me a little sugar...
来  来  来
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
你好吗
How you doing?
抱歉要再麻烦你一次
I'm sorry to do this to you again...
你可以替我照顾一下本吗
...but is there any way you can look after Ben for a little bit?
学校里要开会
I've got this meeting at school.
他说要找"搞笑的"瑞秋阿姨
And he asked for his "fun" Aunt Rachel.
当然可以
Well, of course I will watch him.
我们会玩得很开心  是不是  本
We have fun, don't we, Ben?
-好  待会见  -好
- Okay, see you later, pal. - Okay.
等一下
Wait a minute.
-本  我不能这么做  -怎么了
- Ben, I can't do it. - What?
不能让他这样走掉  他还要开会
Can't let him go out that way. He's got a meeting.
真好  好极了
That's great. That is great.
本  我刚才跟你说什么来着
What did we just finish talking about, Ben?
"本  我刚才跟你说什么来着"
"What did we just finish talking about, Ben?"
我忍无可忍了  过来
All right, that's it. Come here.
你麻烦大了  小伙子
You are in big trouble young man!
本  过来  我没跟你开玩笑
Ben, come here! I am not kidding!
你不能再...
You gotta stop doing...
我的天啊
My God!